<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Software Security from ⊤ to ⊥</title>
    <link>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Software Security from ⊤ to ⊥</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2023, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:29:43 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:29:43 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/talks/</guid>
      <description>Talks I&amp;rsquo;ve given.&#xA;Hot Fuzz: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve got grey, or&amp;hellip; white[box fuzzers]&amp;rdquo;. Australian Reverse Engineering and Vulnerability Research (AUREVR), Jun. 2022.&#xA;Seed Selection for Successful Fuzzing. CSIRO&amp;rsquo;s Data61 &amp;amp; DST Cyber Security Summer School (CSSS), Feb. 2022.&#xA;Analyzing Trigger-Based Malware with S2E. Malware Reverse Engineering (MRE), Jul. 2019.&#xA;Optimizing Away JavaScript Obfuscation. BSides Canberra, Mar. 2019.&#xA;Program Analysis for Reverse Engineers: from ⊤ to ⊥. BSides Canberra, Mar. 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academics</title>
      <link>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/academics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:44:19 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/academics/</guid>
      <description>A summary of my academic endeavours.&#xA;Publications Conference Proceedings Workshop Proceedings Journal Publications Technical Reports Service Publications Conference Proceedings Make out like a (Multi-Armed) Bandit: Improving the Odds of Fuzzer Seed Scheduling with T-Scheduler. Simon Luo, Adrian Herrera, Paul Quirk, Michael Chase, Damith C. Ranasinghe, and Salil S. Kanhere. In AsiaCCS&#39;24: Asia Computer and Communications Security.&#xA;Evocatio: Conjuring Bug Capabilities from a Single PoC. Zhiyuan Jiang, Shuitao Gan, Adrian Herrera, Flavio Toffalini, Lucio Romerio, Chaojing Tang, Manuel Egele, Chao Zhang, and Mathias Payer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://adrianherrera.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! 👋&#xA;My name is Adrian. I am a security researcher interested in applying program analysis techniques to reverse engineering and software security problems. I have a penchant for functional programming languages. This blog is mainly about those things.&#xA;In addition to my day job as a researcher at Interrupt Labs I also teach software security to undergraduates at the Australian National University (ANU). ANU is also where I completed my PhD, under the supervision of Tony Hosking (ANU), Michael Norrish (ANU), and Mathias Payer (EPFL).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
